Guide to the Edward Robb Ellis Papers ca. 1902-1998 MSS 68 MSS 068
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Media
  - A Diary of the Century Edward Robb Ellis on Good Morning America. 68.0141, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
    VHS, Maxell
  - Eddie Ellis on Peter Jennings, ABC February 21, 1996. 68.0142 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    VHS, Maxell HGX-Gold T120
  - Ellis News Interviews, two copies. 68.0143 and 68.0144, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
    VHS, Funi high quality, T-120
  - News Interviews, 68.0145, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
    VHS, Konica high performance E-30
  - Sallie O'D, 68.0146, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
    VHS, Kodak high grade T-120
  - Songs of Leonard Cohen- Last Holiday. 68.0147, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    VHS, TDK extra high grade
  - Eric Hoffer: the crowded life by Jeanne Wolf and Shep Morgan. 68.0148, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
    VHS, 3M T-120
  - Moments Without Proper Names, Jeanne Wolf and Shep Morgan. 68.0149, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Playboy's Playmate Bloopers. 68.0150, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    VHS, 30 min
  - Interview of Edward Robb Ellis by Bill Dagg for Mutual Broadcasting System...Tues, June 30, 1970. 68.0151 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    7 inch reel magnetic tape, Scotch brand, recorded at 7.5
  - New York, New York hosted by Arlene Francis, Guest Edward Robb Ellis. Broadcast May 26, 1982. 68.0152 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    7inch reel magnetic tape, unknown brand or length
  - Unlabeled, 68.0153, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
    5 inch reel Scotch brand magnetic tape, 600 feet.
  - Jo and George Alley, Jerry Lord, Helen and Murray Lubell for the Ellises. 68.0154, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
    5 inch reel, Pentron, 600 feet
  - Stutterer Harry Gordon hypnotized. 68.0155, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
    5 inch reel, Scotch magnetic tape, 600 feet
  - Voice letter to Eddie and Ruth, 68.0156, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
    7 inch reel, magnetic audiotape, 1250 feet.
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 1 and 2 of 7 68.0157 and 68.0158, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
    5 inch reel, magnetic audiotape, unknown brand or length
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 3 and 4 of 7. 68.0159 and 68.0160, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 5 and 6 of 7. 68.0161 and 68.0162, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reel 7 of 7. 68.0163, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Illegible label, two reels. 68.0164 and 68.0165, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
    5 inch reel magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, 600 feet
  - Mounted color transparencies featureing Edward Robb Ellis, Ruth Kraus Ellis, fireworks and cityscapes., undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
    Mounted color transparencies, number 120 film
- Oversize - Series I: Diary
  Oversize materials from Series I: Diary.
  - 1930-1942 (Box 40)
  - 1943-1948 (Box 41)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 42)
  - 1951-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
- Oversize - Series II: Subject Files
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series II: Subject files. Contents are organized alphabetically by first letter.
  - Images, Undated (Box 44)
  - Miscellaneous, including framed photographs, clippings and portraits, undated (Box 45)
  - Portrait of Ruth, framed, undated (Box 46)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 47)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 48)
  - Promotion poster for Diary of a Century, undated (Box Map case)
  - framed clipping, undated (Box Map case)
- Oversize - Series III: Book Typescripts
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series III: Book Typescripts. Contents are organized alphabetically by title.
  - Diary of a Century, Echoes of a Distant Thunder, undated (Box 49)